(Amy:)Honestly, I just
want you to be quiet
(Amy:)but I'm all out of taffy.
(Howard:)You busy?
(Howard:)There's somebody out here
who wants to meet you.
(Bernadette:)Who is it?
(Howard:)Say hello to everybody's
little friend--
(Howard:)remote control
Stephen Hawking!
(Bernadette:)Where did you get that?
(Howard:)I found him in an old box.
(Bernadette:)Why would you buy it?
(Howard:)I didn't buy it.
(Howard:)I made it.
(Bernadette:)Last question.
(Bernadette:)What is wrong with you?
(Howard:)What's the big deal?
(Bernadette:)Howie, it's in poor taste.
(Howard:)No, it's not.
Check it out.
(Howard:)He says fun stuff.
(Remote-control Hawking:)Hey good lookin',
(Remote-control Hawking:)want to go for a spin?
(Howard:)His eyes also light up
in the dark.